### Contact

310-721-2004 (Mobile) jath10-14@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/janegutierrez-7a630354 (LinkedIn) www.4SW.com (Company)

### Top Skills

ICU

Hospitals

Nursing

### Certifications

Extra Corporeal Membrane Oxygenation; Basic Life Support; Pediatric Basic Life Support; Neonatal Life Support

# Jane Gutierrez

Clinical level 3, ECMO Specialist at Children's Hospital Los Angeles (CHLA) BSN, RN, CCRN

Hawthorne, California

# Summary

I am passionate about giving back to the youth around me and giving back to the community. I believe in leading by example with mentoring and teaching. I believe in experiencing life to the fullest and allowing others to enjoy the same experiences as I have.

## Experience

**CHLA** 

38 years 7 months

Clinical Nurse 111, ECMO Specialist, BSN, RN, CCRN December 2016 - Present (3 years 7 months)

4650 Sunset Blvd. Los Angeles, CA 90027

Registered Nurse level 111; Relief Charge Nurse December 1981 - December 2016 (35 years 1 month)

4650 Sunset Blvd. Los Angeles, CA 90027

Over 35 years in Clinical Nursing in both hospital and public health settings. Main focus has been in a high level newborn intensive care unit at Children's Hospital Los Angeles. Clinical expertise include extra corporeal membrane oxygenation, team leading, resource, mentoring, teaching, orientation, and relief charge nurse. Strategic leadership positions include board membership, vice presidencies, and presidencies of not-for-profit organizations (Four Seasons West Ski and Snowboard Club; The Honor Society of Nursing, Sigma Theta Tau International, Nu Mu Chapter; Far West Ski Association).

Specialties: High Risk Newborn Intensive Care, Strategic Planning for nonprofit volunteer organizations, Communications, Public Speaking, Event Planning

Clinical Nurse 111
December 1981 - December 2016 (35 years 1 month)
4650 Sunset Blvd. Los Angeles, CA 90027

Children's Hospital Los Angeles (CHLA) ECMO Specialist December 2016 - Present (3 years 7 months)

The Honor Society of Nursing, Sigma Theta Tau International Board member and Fundraising Chair May 2008 - May 2012 (4 years 1 month)

Developed and implemented fundraising strategies and events for student scholarships at California State University Los Angeles. The student recipients were also members of STT.

Four Seasons West Ski and Snowboard Club Board Member September 2000 - September 2010 (10 years 1 month)

Strategic planning and implementation of fundraising events for the organization. Held several leadership positions to assist in coordination of events (new membership orientation, race director, trip leader, and committee chairperson).

## Education

California State University-Los Angeles
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (1980 - 1983)

**UCLA** 

· (1977 - 1980)